♪ ♪
Susan Prescott: Welcome to the WWDC 24Platforms State of the Union!
WWDC is always an exciting time of year when we dig into the technical details
of what we've been working on,share how it works,
and help you understandwhat's possible in your apps and games.
Before we get started,we want to take a moment
to recognize your hard work and dedication--
you are the creators, designers,and developers
of the amazing apps and games that people use every day
to learn, play, work,and change the world.
Thank you!
We love connecting with you around the world
at Apple Developer Centers,Developer Academies,
and Apple Vision Pro labs
where you created the first spatial computing apps and games!
And the next generation of developers blew us away
in the Swift Student Challenge with clever, creative playgrounds
that tackled topics from social impact to security.